<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide Activity</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
    <string name="eat">Eat</string>
    <string name="sleep">Sleep</string>
    <string name="drink">Drink</string>
    <string name="toronto">Toronto</string>
    <string name="toronto_desc">Toronto, the capital of the province of Ontario, is a major Canadian city along Lake Ontario\'s northwestern shore. It\'s a dynamic metropolis with a core of soaring skyscrapers, all dwarfed by the iconic, free-standing CN Tower. Toronto also has many green spaces, from the orderly oval of Queen’s Park to 400-acre High Park and its trails, sports facilities and zoo.</string>
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="downtown">Downtown</string>
    <string name="east_york">East York</string>
    <string name="scarborough">Scarborough</string>
    <string name="north_york">North York</string>
    <string name="etobicoke">Etobicoke</string>
    <string name="places_go">Where to Go</string>
    <string name="places_eat">Where to Eat</string>
    <string name="places_sleep">Where to Sleep</string>
    <string name="places_drink">Where to Drink</string>
    <string name="detail">"detail"</string>
    <string name="type">"type"</string>
    <string name="hotel">"hotel"</string>
    <string name="restaurant">"restaurant"</string>
    <string name="tourist">"tourist"</string>
    <string name="directions_prefix">http://maps.google.com/maps?f=d&amp;daddr=</string>
    <string name="call_prefix">tel:</string>
    <string name = "royal_york">Fairmont Royal York</string>
    <string name = "ry_address">100 Front Street West Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="ry_description">Occupying a circa-1929 building retaining original features such as hand-painted ceilings and travertine pillars, this upscale hotel is a 13-minute walk from the CN Tower and 1 km from the Harbourfront Centre.\n\nElegant rooms offer Wi-Fi (fee) and flat-screen TVs, as well as minibars, and tea and coffeemakers; some have city views. Upgraded rooms add sitting areas. Individually decorated suites include living rooms; some have wet bars or full kitchens and dining rooms.\n\nThere are 4 restaurants and bars, including a refined lounge serving afternoon tea. There\'s also a spa with a 24/7 gym, an indoor pool and a whirlpool tub.\n</string>
    <string name="ry_website">https://www.fairmont.com/royal-york-toronto/</string>
    <string name = "ry_number">4163682511</string>
    <string name = "marriott">Toronto Airport Marriott Hotel</string>
    <string name = "marriott_address">901 Dixon Road Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="marriott_description">This upscale hotel is 4 km from Toronto Pearson International Airport and 6 km from Centennial Park.\n\nThe polished rooms have flat-screen TVs, desks, and tea and coffeemaking facilities. Wi-Fi is available. Some rooms have access to a lounge with free continental breakfast and evening appetizers. Suites add living areas.\n\nThere\'s a restaurant serving Canadian cuisine, and a Starbucks, as well as an indoor pool, a whirlpool tub and a fitness center. Other amenities include meeting rooms and a business center.\n</string>
    <string name="marriott_website">https://www.marriott.com/hotels/travel/yyz-toronto-airport-marriott-hotel/</string>
    <string name = "marriott_number">4166749400</string>
    <string name = "shangrila">Shangri-La Hotel</string>
    <string name = "shangrila_address">188 University Ave Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="shangrila_description">This upscale, Asian-inspired hotel in a sleek modern building is a 2-minute walk from Osgoode subway station, a 12-minute walk from the Art Gallery of Ontario and a 15-minute walk from the CN Tower.\n\nThe polished Asian-inspired rooms offer free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and iPod docks, plus minibars, Nespresso machines, and marble bathrooms with designer toiletries. Luxe 1- and 2-bedroom suites add separate living rooms with pull-out sofas, and 1 features a balcony and a dining room. Room service is available.\n\nThere\'s a chic Asian restaurant, a cocktail bar, and a slick lobby lounge with a tea menu, plus a spa, a fitness centre and an indoor pool.\n</string>
    <string name="shangrila_website">https://www.shangri-la.com/toronto/shangrila/</string>
    <string name = "shangrila_number">6477888888</string>
    <string name = "kingyo">Kingyo Izakaya</string>
    <string name = "kingyo_address">51b Winchester Street Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="kingyo_description">Kingyo Izakaya serves up an extensive menu of boxed sushi, stone bowls, chicken wings and other izakaya eats in Cabbagetown.\n</string>
    <string name="kingyo_website">http://kingyotoronto.com</string>
    <string name = "kingyo_number">6475035248</string>
    <string name = "remezzo">Remezzo Italian Bistro</string>
    <string name = "remezzo_address">3335 Sheppard Avenue E Scarborough, ON</string>
    <string name="remezzo_description">Casual eatery with Impressionist art &amp; warm wood tones, serving Italian staples plus ribs &amp; steaks.\n</string>
    <string name="remezzo_website">http://www.remezzo.ca</string>
    <string name = "remezzo_number">4164988848</string>
    <string name = "ruths_chris">Ruth\'s Chris</string>
    <string name = "rc_address">145 Richmond Street Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="rc_description">Get the best steak house experience at Ruth\'s Chris Steak House in Toronto, Ontario. Our signature 500° sizzling plates and award-winning wine list are the perfect pairing for any occasion. Whether you\’re joining us for a romantic dinner, a business meeting, a private party or just a drink at the bar, our Toronto steak house will deliver superior service and an unforgettable dining experience.\n</string>
    <string name="rc_website">https://ruthschris.ca/toronto/</string>
    <string name = "rc_number">6475035248</string>
    <string name="italian">Italian</string>
    <string name="japanese">Japanese</string>
    <string name="steakhouse">Steakhouse</string>
    <string name="lounge">Lounge</string>
    <string name="gamebar">Game Bar</string>
    <string name="brewpub">Brewpub</string>
    <string name = "cn_tower">CN Tower</string>
    <string name = "cntower_address">290 Bremner Blvd Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="cntower_description">Discover the thrilling views over Toronto and Lake Ontario from three observation levels including the LookOut and SkyPod. Stretching out to the horizon, visibility on a clear day can reach 160km.\n\nSavour the wonderful regional cuisine of the award-winning 360 Restaurant. Pair your meal with a wine from the collection in the World’s Highest Wine Cellar. Enjoy other dining options at the CN Tower: choose from a variety of food and beverage with a Canadian focus available on the LookOut level; and located at the base of the CN Tower, Le Café caters to a wide array of tastes, providing a delicious range of reasonably priced fresh market fare and beverages ideal for visitors and those on the go.\n</string>
    <string name="cntower_website">http://www.cntower.ca</string>
    <string name = "cntower_number">4168686937</string>
    <string name = "casa_loma">Casa Loma</string>
    <string name = "casaloma_address">1 Austin Terrace Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="casaloma_description">Casa Loma is a Gothic Revival style mansion and garden in midtown Toronto, Ontario, Canada, that is now a historic house museum and landmark. It was constructed from 1911 to 1914 as a residence for financier Sir Henry Pellatt. The architect was E. J. Lennox, who designed several other city landmarks.\n\nCasa Loma is one of Toronto’s top tourist attractions and hospitality venues. Each year over 350,000 visitors tour Casa Loma and the estate gardens. A perfect backdrop for special occasions, Casa Loma also plays host to over 250 private events annually. The unique architecture has also made it a highly desirable location for film, television and photo shoots.\n\nCasa Loma prides itself on historical preservation and mindfulness of the past. Casa Loma features permanent installations such as: our Dark Side of Toronto photo exhibit; and Classic Car Collection in Casa Loma’s Stables, in-line with the castle’s heyday. Casa Loma also curates special exhibits on a regular basis, pertaining to early Toronto and Canadian history.\n</string>
    <string name="casaloma_website">https://www.casaloma.ca</string>
    <string name = "casaloma_number">4169231171</string>
    <string name = "zoo">Toronto Zoo</string>
    <string name = "zoo_address">2000 Meadowvale Rd Scarborough, ON</string>
    <string name="zoo_description">The Toronto Zoo is a zoo located in Scarborough. Encompassing 287 hectares (710 acres), the Toronto Zoo is the largest zoo in Canada. It is divided into seven zoogeographic regions: Indo-Malaya, Africa, Americas, Tundra Trek, Australasia, Eurasia, and the Canadian Domain. Some animals are displayed indoors in pavilions and outdoors in what would be their naturalistic environments, with viewing at many levels. It also has areas such as the Kids Zoo, Waterside Theatre, and Splash Island. It has one of the most taxonomically diverse collection of animals on display of any zoo; it is currently home to over 5,000 animals (including invertebrates and fish) representing over 500 species. The zoo is open to the public every day of the year except December 25.\n</string>
    <string name="zoo_website">http://www.torontozoo.com</string>
    <string name = "zoo_number">4163925900</string>
    <string name = "bar_raval">Bar Raval</string>
    <string name = "barraval_address">505 College Street Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="barraval_description">A Barcelona-inspired pinxto  bar with small plates to share and a variety of cocktails, beer, wine and fortifieds.</string>
    <string name="barraval_website">https://www.thisisbarraval.ca</string>
    <string name = "barraval_number">6473448001</string>
    <string name = "time_capsule">Time Capsule Board Games Cafe &amp; Bar</string>
    <string name = "tc_address">2183 Danforth Ave Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="tc_description">Play games. Have drinks. Eat Food. Have a kick ass party! Great for families, friends or work staff. Board Games. Video Games. Pool. Ping Pong. Foosball. Low-key spot offering many board games, arcade games &amp; table games, plus bar food &amp; beer.</string>
    <string name="tc_website">https://www.timecapsulebgc.com</string>
    <string name = "tc_number">4166668875</string>
    <string name = "aviary">The Aviary</string>
    <string name = "aviary_address">484A Front St E Toronto, ON</string>
    <string name="aviary_description">Scratch-made snacks &amp; sandwiches served in an airy brewpub with plenty of TVs &amp; an expansive patio.</string>
    <string name="aviary_website">https://www.aviarybrewpub.com</string>
    <string name = "aviary_number">6473527837</string>
</resources>
